Guide to the Julian C. Smith papers, 1900-2015.
Smith, Julian C. papers
- Series VII. Organizations & Committees
  - Organizations
    - Ithaca Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1952-05-21-1954-01-01 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Opera Association, 1963-03-01-1971-03-26 (Box 5, Folder 42)
      Includes correspondence, show programs, meeting minutes
    - The Magic Flute - Ticket Sales, 1964-08-1964-11 (Box 5, Folder 44)
      Organized by the Ithaca Civic Opera Association
    - Tosca - Ticket Sales, 1965-01-30-1965-04-12 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - American Institute of Chemical Engineers, 1972-09-14-1984-07 (Box 5, Folder 15)
      Includes reports, correspondence, call for papers, other materials
    - American Society for Engineering Education, 1973-07-11-1978-03-21 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Cornell Research Club, 1974-09-1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
      Includes speaker schedule, correspondence, membership lists
    - Engineering Foundation, 1976-1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - American Chemical Society, 1976-08-10-1985-09-27 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Statler Club, 1978-09-06-1979-01-17 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - American Chemical Society, 1984-10-18-1986-01 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Annual AIChE Meeting, 1984-11 (Box 5, Folder 22)
      San Francisco, California
    - American Chemical Society, 1985-04-26-1986-04-15 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - American Chemical Society, 1986-04-16-1988-10 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Annual AIChE Meeting, 1987-10-12-1987-11-17 (Box 5, Folder 21)
      New York, New York
    - Environmental Careers Organization, 1993-1994-03 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Committees
    - American Society of Mechanical Engineers Bulk Solids Flow Committee, 1952-05-23-1959-06-12 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      Includes correspondence, meeting reports, bulletins, meeting minutes, committee report, by-laws
    - College of Engineering Dean Committee, 1957-11-05-1965-08-25 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - College of Engineering Dean Committee, 1958-02-19-1959-03-24 (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - College of Engineering Dean Committee, 1958-05-23-1964-04-20 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committees, 1960-10-02-1964-03-03 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Vaughn Behn Ad Hoc Committee, 1962-10-24-1962-11-21 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - College of Engineering Dean Committee, 1963-10-11-1964-08-21 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Engineering College Study Committee, 1963-11-14-1964-05-27 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Master of Chemical Engineering Committee, 1964-06-12-1965-05-19 (Box 7, Folder 20)
      Includes notes, memoranda, correspondence, minutes
    - Liggett & Henkel Ad Hoc Committees, 1965-01-07-1965-02-23 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - M. I. Esrig Ad Hoc Committee, 1966-02-14-1966-03-01 (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - Master of Chemical Engineering Committee, 1970-12-09-1975-10-28 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      Includes memoranda, announcements, notes, reports, proposals
    - AIChE Centrifuge Symposium & Centrifuge & Mixer Testing Committee, 1971-03-31-1980-08-15 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Graduate Professional Programs Committee, 1973-05-14-1983-03-16 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      Includes minutes, reports, summaries, correspondence
    - Ross McFarlane Ad Hoc Committee, 1974-03-20-1974-04-26 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - AIChE Filter Committee, 1975-08-04-1978-12-13 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - F. J. Ahimaz Ad Hoc Committee, 1975-08-15-1976-01-13 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Commencement 1976, 1976-03-02-1976-06-01 (Box 7, Folder 1)
      Includes commencement instructions & arrangements, program, memoranda
    - Graduate Professional Programs Committee Material, 1976-03-17-1981-04-27 (Box 7, Folder 21)
      Includes minutes, reports, correspondence, memoranda
    - Neil Orloff Ad Hoc Committee, 1976-09-24-1978-07-24 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Commencement 1977, 1977-03-17-1977-06-03 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Commencement 1978, 1978-03-22-1978-06-13 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Commencement 1979, 1978-12-20-1979-05-29 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Engineering Faculty Salaries Ad Hoc Committee, 1979-03 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Commencement 1980, 1980-02-29-1981-01-16 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Space & Safety Committee, 1981-1984-06-29 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Commencement 1981, 1981-05-13-1981-06-08 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Chemical Engineering Kirkpatrick Award Committee, 1982-05-14-1983-02-01 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Commencement 1982, 1982-05-21-1982-05-30 (Box 7, Folder 7)
      Includes programs, memorandum
    - American Chemical Society Nominating Committee, 1984-03-06-1986-09-10 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Chemical Engineering Personal Achievement Award, 1986-04-15-1994-07-13 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Employee Benefits Advisory Committee, 1991-09-09-1993-06-17 (Box 7, Folder 13)
      Includes correspondence, meeting notes, project drafts
- Series VIII. Media
  - Untitled, undated; V-9370 (Box 1)
  - A History of the School of Chemical Engineering, V-9369 (Box 1)
- Series IX. Separated Materials
  - Cornellian, 1941; Cornell University
  - The Legacy of Dale R. Corson DVD, 2009; University Press
    Available as a part of Internet-First University Press collection, #6746
    Ithaca, NY